Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2014-100
  - Sobrato Family Foundation Annual Report, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "A Life Devoted to Teaching Others How to Give, From the Grassroots UP", 2000 Dec. 14 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - e-Philantrhropy From Entrepreneurial Adventure to an Online Community, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NFG Reports: Philantrhropy Supports Equity and Smart Growth, 2001 June 23 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - News: Women & Philanthropy Volume 24, Number 2, 2001 July 27 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Women & Philanthropy Letter about Newsletter and The Meaning and Impact of Board and Staff Diversity, 2001 July 27 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rasing Our Voices, 2001 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation Wimen's Philanthropy, 1980 Sept. 5 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Flora Family Fondation Gap Project: Domestic Initiative, 2000 Feb. 4 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Funding All Women: Including Women and Girls with Disabilities, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Rasing Our Voices, 2000 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Palo Alto demographics statistics and maps, 1990-2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Women & Philanthropy, 25th anniv, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - EPA Can Do, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Silicon valley Community Foundation, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Land Trust Group, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Benton Foundation Annual Report, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - California Wellness Foundation, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - TFI Update: The Foundation Incubator, 2002 Aug. 3 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Email: Photo of Jing Lyman, 2005 Sept. 25 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Women & Philanthropy Letter About 2003-2004 Membership Directory, 2003 Nov. 25 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Email: Resehduled Host Committee Conference Call, 2002 Oct. 24 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - The Next 25 Years of Women & Philanthropy: Women's Health and Economic Justice, 2003 Jan. 23 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - GBN: What Environment Might We Be Working in?, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Scenarios: A Select Bibliography, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Women & Philanthropy California Regional Meeting Attendee List, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Women & Philanthropy California Regional Meeting Attendee List Addenum, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Women & Philanthropy Communications Survey, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Various Letters and Forms for Women & Philanthropy, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Letters and Info About "The Next 25 Years of Women & Philantrhopy: Women's Health and Economic Justice in California, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Short Note About Kim's Invite Letter, 2002 Nov. 27 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Copy of Invitation to Dr. Ramphele/World Bank, 2002 Dec. 10 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Email: Follow-Up/Hello, 2003 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - The Enterprise Foundation and Women & Philanthropy Plans, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Emails between meghan McCleary and Jing Lyman, 2002 May-June (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Email: Packet, 2002 June 17 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Email from Lyman to McCleary, 2002 May 19 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Letters and Emails About Afghan Women's Committee, 2002 May (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Letters Sent to Enterprise, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Letter about Charitable Expenses, 2002 July 16 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Emails: 2003 Annual Meeting Planning Committee, Your Card, 2002 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Meesage from Women & Philanthropy, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - FW Memberships and W&P 2003 Annual Meeting Host Committee, 2002 Aug.-Nov. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Women & Philanrthropy Newsletter Volume 26, 2002 Summer (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Getting Started: An Early History of Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy, 2002 April (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Women & Philanthropy: Newsletter, Faxes, and Letters, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Women & Philanthropy: Newletter and Pamphlets, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Women & Philanthropy 2003 Annual Meeting Planning Commitee, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Letter from Women & Philanthropy to Lyman, 2002 Oct. 3 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Letter about Renewing your Individual Partnershop with Women & Philanthropy, 2003 March 31 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Kimberly Otis as President of Women & Philanthropy, 2002 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Letter from Lyman to Cavanaugh, Hagan & Pierson, Inc., Member Services, and "Adventure in Venture Philanthropy", 2001 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Thank You Letter from McCleary to Lyman, 2000 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Letter Announcing Christine Grumm as WFN's Executive Director, 2000 April 27 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - American Leadership Forum, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Council on Foundations 52nd Annual Conference Philadelphia, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Building Leadership For the Next 25 Years Pamphlet, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Call for Sessions, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - When I Dare to Be Powerful, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - The White House Project, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women Newsletter, 2002 Summer (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - The Collabortative Fund Model: Effectice Strategies for Grantmaking, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Ms Foundation for Women Annual report and Highlights for Fiscal year, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Rosenburg Foundation Report, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Rosenburg Foundation, 2000-2005 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - The Vision to Lead. the Power to Move. The Potential to Change the World Annual Report, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Women's Funding Network Annual Report, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Short Note with Phone Number, 2003 Dec. 15 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Letter from Women's Funding Network to Lyman, 2003 Oct. 15 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Global Fund for Female, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Fax from Whitehurts to Lyman, 2003 Dec. 18 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Women's Funding Network, 2003 Dec. 17 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women Annual Report, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Women's Pitsenc Women's Fund South Africa, 2000 May (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Women of Silicon Valley Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - 2002 Women of Silicon Valley (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Untapped Potential: Women's Civic Leadership in Silicon Valley, 2002 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - San Jose Mercury News Opinion: Beyond Ward and June Cleaver, 2001 April 23 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Untapped Potential: Women's Civic Leadership in Silicon Valley, 2002 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Thank You Letter to Jing for Launching "Unfinished Business: Women in the Silicon valley Economy", 2001 May 22 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Unfinished Business: Women in the Silicon Valley Economy, 2001 April (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Letter from Patti to Jing and Richard Lyman, 2006 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Building a More Just & Equitable Society, 2005 Nov. 28 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Envelope with Ground Breakers Dream Makers, 2005 Sept. 6 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Strong Women Making a Difference, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Note About "Unstopped Potential", 2002 March 4 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - The Women's Foundation of California 25 Years, 2004 March 23 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Women's Foundation of Claifonia's 25th Anniversary Gala, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - 2002 The Women's FDN (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - The Women's Foundation: Notes and "The World Belongs to Us, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - The Women's Foundation Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Letter from Tribal Voice to Jing Lyman, 2001 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - On the Level Volume 7 Number 1, Fall 2000 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Every Counts Annual Report Highlights, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Southland Social, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Letter from Enterprise to Lyman with "Wicked" Flyer, 2006 Oct. 27 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Memorial Service for Cushing Dolbeare, 2005 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Letter to Joan Bisset/ Vice President of External Affairs Leaving, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Joan Bisset and Harvey bart Letters, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Building Commitees of Opportunity Campaign, 2005 March (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Enterprise Foundations's Building Communities of Opportunity Campaign Update, 2005 March 17 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Community Land Trusts Fundees Brietine, 2001 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Trust for Housing Initiative, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - PIA Community News and Views, 2001 Winter (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Enterprise Board Buddies, 2008 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Beltline, 2008 July (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Enterprise Name Change, 2005 Dec. 16 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - The Politics of Housing, 2005 Nov. 15 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Enterprise Gulf Coast Report No. 1, 2005 Dec. 15 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Financial Statements in The Enterprise Social Investment Corporation and Sunsidaries, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Letter to Lyman and Enterprise: Defining Success, 2005 Oct. 10 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - The Enterprise Social Investment Corporation and Subsidaries, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - The Enterprise Foundation Board oof Trustees Board Evaluation, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2005 Aug. 9 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Letter from Lyman to Davis, 2005 Aug. 12 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Green Communities, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Enterprise Foundation Faxes and Memorandums Involving Requests, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Building Opportunities of Opportunity Campaign, 2005 April (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Notes with Phone Numbers, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2005 March 10 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Enterprise Value Statements, undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Dates, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - The Enterprise Foundation Inc. Conflicts of Interest Policy Disclosure Statement, 2005 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Memo: Conflicts of Interest Policy, 2005 March 10 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Letter from Harvey to Kibbee, 2005 Feb. 15 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Letter from Harvey to Canales, 2005 Feb. 15 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Recommendations for Enterprise Board, 2004 July 13 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Roles and Responsibilities for Enterprise Foundation Board Members, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Letter about Proposed Schedule of Board of Trustee Meetings, 2004 June 22 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Fax from Harvey to Lyman, 2004 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Letter from Lyman to Montague, 2004 April 18 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Trip Enterprise Wash D.C., 2004 March (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - The Enterprise Foundation's Building Communities of Choice Campiagn Trustees Monthly Update, 2005 Jan. 24 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Executive Committee Conference Call, 2005 Jan. 13 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2004 Dec. 1 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - 2004 Election Analysis, 2004 Nov. 8 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Letter about Chairman's and President's Reports, 2004 Nov. 23 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2004 Dec. 1 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2004 March 10 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - The Board of Trustees Meeting of the Financial Review and Auidit Committee, 2004 March 9 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Contibutions Recipients, 2003 Sept. 17 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - LKS Wed./Thurs. Dr. Richard Lyman, 1981 Sept. 24 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Community Partners Papers, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Fax Memo: Board of Trustee Meeting Follow Up, 2006 Sept. 21 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Fax Memo: Profile in Enterprise News, 2006 Aug. 29 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Fax Memo: Mark Cavanaugh's Departure, 2006 July 28 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - San Jose Mercury News: Gaining Ground on Affordable Housing, 2006 July 24 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Letter to Jing S. Lyman from Fannie Mae Foundation, 2006 Aug. 10 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Letter to Trustees, 2006 Aug. 10 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - San Jose Mercury News: Green Tech's Growth, 2006 Aug. 6 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Fax Memo: Michael Neely to join Enterprise As Interim CFO, 2006 Aug. 7 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Fax memo: Announcement of Terri Y. Montague's Appointment as President and CEO of Atlanta Beltline, 2006 July 14 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - New York Board Meeting Letter, 2006 June 21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Fax Memo: Draft Profile for Enterprise Newsletter, 2006 July 10 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Letter from Enterprise about A New Approach, 2006 June (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Update, 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Washington Post Articles, 2006 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Real Estate Leadership Council, 2006 May 4 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Enterprise Community Partners Trustees Gulf Coast Tour. May 9-10, 2006 April 7 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Enterprise Update, 2006 March 31 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Progress from Last Week's Board and Committee Meetings, 2006 March 24 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Note about Gulf Coast Report, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Letters from Lyman to politicians, 2006 April 3 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2006 March 7 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Enterprise Community Partners, Inc. Board of Trustees Executive Commitee, 2006 March 14 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Enterpise Community Partners, Inc. Board of Trustees Metting, 2006 Macrh 15 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Board of Trustees Finanical Review Committee Coference Call, 2006 March 13 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Enterprise Community Partners Resources Development Commitee, 2006 Feb. 13 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Board of Trustees Resource Devlopment Comittee Meeting, 2006 March 6 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Enterprise, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Confidential Memo, 2006 Jan. 30 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Bart Harvey's Itinerary, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Bart's Northern California Itinerary, 2005 Feb. 4 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - RE: Enterprise Green Communities Initiative, 2004 Aug. 31 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Monthly Email Campaign Update to the Board, 2004 July 14 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Community Gardens in New York, 2004 July 12 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - New York's Community Gardens - A Resource at Risk, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Building Communities of Opportunity Campaign Board Discussion Session, 2003 March 6 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2002 Nov. 19 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Letter from Harvey to the Enterprise Foundation Board of Trustees, 2003 March 11 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - The President's Jobs and Growth Package and Low-Income Housing, 2003 March 11 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Initial Response to White Paper on Dividend Proposal, 2003 March 11 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Letter from Minow to Hapke, 2003 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Statement by the Board of Trustees of teh Enterpirse Foundation, 2003 March 7 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Leadership Is Award, 2003 Jan. 29 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Fax from Gudzowsky to Lyman about IS Leadership Award, 2003 Jan. 27 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Trustee Survey on Virtual Board Meetings, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Metlife Foundation Older Volunteers Enrich America Awards, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Leadershio IS Award, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Summary Presented During Trustee Meeting, 2002 Dec. 11 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Mortgage Letter, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Board Meeting Dates, 2002 July 11 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Charting a Course for the Next Decade in Community Development, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Letter from Lyman to Montague, 2002 July 16 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Share Our Security, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - The Enterprise Foundation, Inc. Conflicts of Interest Policy Disclosure Statement, 2002 March (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Conference at a Glance, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Letter from Cullman to Mr. and Mrs. Richard Lyman, 2002 Feb. 25 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Letter from Lyman to Koo, Whitehurst, 2001 Aug. 26 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Letter from Lyman to Bing, 2001 Aug. 5 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Letter from Bell to Lyman, 2001 June 19 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Letter from Bell to Lyman, 2001 June 14 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - The Enterprise Foundation Names New President, Cheif Operating Officer, 2001 June 14 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Notification oof Enterprise Executive Commitee of the Board Conference Call, 2001 June 5 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Background for Confernce Call, 2001 June 6 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2001 June 22 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Bank of America: Letter from Bessant to Lyman, 2001 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2001 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Older American's Attitudes about Community, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Revised 2001 Board Dates, 2001 Jan 23 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Choices for Executive Commitee & Financial Review & Audit Committee Dinner, 2001 April 23 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - The Enterprise Foundation: Gary Gensler accepted offer to join Board of Trustees, 2001 Jun 21 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - The Enterprise Foundation: Withdrawal of grant from the Packard Foundation, 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Nancy on vacation, 2001 Jun 26 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Letter to Sterling Speirn, 2001 Feb 5 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - The Enterprise Foundation: Letter from Harvey to Lyman, 2001 Jan 16 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Letter to Peter Bing from Jing Lyman, 2001 Jan 12 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Letter from Ricki to Jing Lyman, 2001 Jan 6 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - The Enterprise Foundation 2000 Annual Report, 2001 Jun 28 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - The Enterprise Foundation: Annual Meeting of Board of Trustees, 2006 Mar 6 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - 2001 Doris Koo Enterprise, 2001 Jan - Jul (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - 6/29-30/2001 Portland Oregon Enterprise, 2001 Jun (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Enterprise 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 97 Enterprise/EPA, 1996-2001 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - James W. Rouse A Nation Remembers A Man of Vision, undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy, 1979-2001 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Emails to Anne and Kirke Wilson from Jing Lyman, 2001 Dec (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Women and Philanthropy, 2001 Oct (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Women and Phil Chicago 7/8-9/2001, 2001 Mar-Oct (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Women and Philanthropy, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Women and Philanthropy email exchange, 2002 Feb-Apr (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Letter to Anne and Kirke Wilson, 2002 Apr 8 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Bellagio Project, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Card from Joyce Ream to Lyman, 2002 Jan 19 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Email exchange with Lisa Croney, 2002 Feb 19 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Women and Philanthropy 25th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Email exchange with Meghan McCleary, 2002 Feb (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Leadership circle letters; emails, 2002 Mar (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Search committee for executive director of Women and Philanthropy, 2002 Mar (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Bellagio project emails, 2002 Mar (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy Publications List, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Address of Joyce Ream, undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Telefax about Estelle Freedman's book, 2002 Mar (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Anne Wilson, 2002 Jan 16 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Foundation for Women: Adolescent Sexuality, 1983 Jun 2 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Survey of Ten Community Foundations' Discretionary Funding, 1979 May (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - NYT article "In Philanthropies, Women Move Up - Slowly", 1980 Aug 8 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Bellagio Project, 2002 Jan 22 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Meghan - chair of founding committee, 2002 Apr 4 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Joyce Yu, 1980 Jan 16 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - The Subtle Revolution: Women at Work, undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Mills College Women's Leadership Institute, 2002 Mar 29 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy, 1979 Jan (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Bay Area Women in Philanthropy, 1980 Jan-Feb (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Letter to Robert Goheen from Lyman, 1975 Sep 16 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Letter to Diane Bancel from Joyce Ream, 1980 Jan 30 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Letter to Diane Bancel from Lyman, 1980 Mar 18 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Letter to Lyman, 1980 May 8 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Women and Foundations Annual Conference, 1978 May 2 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Women and Foundations: Of Special Interest, 1977 Dec (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Women and Foundations: Invitation to Pre-Conference Luncheon, 1976 Apr 7 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Women and Foundations: Pre-Conference Workshops Questions, undated (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Reimbursement of Airfare, undated (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Women and Materials, 2001 Jun (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - WAF/CP United Nations Decade for Women, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Women in Foundations and Funding Feminists, 1978 Oct 1 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Foundations Step Up Funding of Job Projects for Women, 1980 Jan 25 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Envelope with Joyce Ream's address written on it, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Women and Foundations catalog, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Email exchange with Holly Antolini, 2002 Jan-Feb (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy Submission Statement, 1978 Oct 20 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Today's girls: tomorrow's women, 1978 Jun 13-15 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - WAF/CP Inequality of Sacrifice, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - WAF/CP Development, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - WAF/CP The Edward W. Hazen Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - WAF/CP Survey of Six Foundations That Derive Their Assets..., 1978 Apr (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - WAF/CP Submission Statement, 1979 Aug 2 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Financial Support for Women's Programs in the 1970s order form, undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Financial Support for Women's Programs in the 1970s, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1979 Jul 10 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - WAF/CP: National Committee on Responsive Philanthropy, 1979 Aug 4 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - WAF/CP: Fundraising Proposal, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - WAF/CP Newsletter Fall 1979 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - WAF/CP: Survey of Community Foundations, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Mother's Day 1980 style, 1980 May 11 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Final Report of the Forums on Women's Funding, 1981 Jan 26 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - WAF/CP: The Subtle Revolution Women at Work luncheon, 1980 Apr 5 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - WAF/CP: Spring luncheon sponsorship, 1980 May 14 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - WAF/CP: Tax Exemption Certificate, 1979 Apr 6 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - WAF/CP: state franchise tax board, undated (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - WAF/CP: Bay Area Women in Philanthropy, 1980 Jan 21 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Letter from Bill Somerville of San Mateo Foundation, 1980 Mar 14 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Letter to Ann Lynch from Diane Bancel, 1980 Mar 30 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - WAF/CP: Forum Series, 1980 Apr 6 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Letter on Interim Report on the Women's Funding Series, 1980 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Interim Report on the Women's Funding Series, undated (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Rosenberg Foundation Grants for Women and Girls, 1980 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Funding for series of women's forums in the bay area, 1981 Oct-Nov (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Seminar on third world women, 1982 Apr 8 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Seminar on rape, incest, and pornography, 1982 Aug 12 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - NYT article "A center where wife batterers are counseled..", 1980 Sep 16 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Income differentials among the aged, 1979 Nov 30 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Women at Work luncheon, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Letter to Martha Golensky from Phyllis Simpkins, The Cambridge Foundation, 1980 Aug 4 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - WAF/CP Urban Institute, 1981 Jan 13 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1980 Apr 30 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Letter from Otto Bremer Foundation re: Joyce Yu's departure, 1979 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 167)